[Title] Futures Friends. Movement break: Elephant Stomp & Sway. Move along with Bop.
Hi, friends! I'm Bop.
Stomp with me! Right, left!
Now sway, sway, like a gentle tree.
One, two! Your turn!
Stomp and sway! Great job!
Freeze... you did it!
Ready? Bop and go!
Let's do it again!
Stomp your heavy elephant feet...
One, two, three!
Now swing your trunk from side to side...
Swish... swish!
Slow... down...
Now you're a sleepy elephant.
Shhh... sleepy elephant.
Good morning, elephant! Time to wake up!
Let's be elephants sitting down.
Everybody can do it!
Pat your knees like elephant feet...
One, two, three!
Now make a big trunk with both arms.
Swing... and swing... and swing!
Ta-da!
Sitting or standing, you did it!
Now let's do it very, very quietly.
Shhh.
Quiet knee pats...
One, two, three.
Now a slow, quiet trunk.
Hum with me. [Bop hums softly]
Now let's stand up tall!
endcard
[End card] Great moving, friends! Learn. Move. Explore. Belong.
A Futures Friends movement break.